Daniel Adeniran

Lagos, Lagos, Nigeria



thedanielsdev@gmail.com



07060563133



linkedin.com/in/daniel-adeniran

Summary

Courteous, enthusiastic solution-driven Web and Mobile Application Developer adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, I am interested in IT and everything in its orbit and I am eagerly ready to bring my present knowledge of Web and Mobile development to make ideas come to reality. I am a Creative thinker and I love to research.

Yours Always.

Experience



Mobile Application Developer

Thedaniels

Jun 2021 - Present (6 months +)

I developed a random wordpair generator app, Which generates random wordpairs from a particular Web Api and also generates new wordpair items on each app refresh.

Each wordpairs can be liked and added to lists of favourite wordpair.

What I Used/Learned in this project:

- 1. Flutter
- 2. Communicating with Web Api's with Flutter
- 3. Developing complex Ui's etc

→ Mobile Application Developer

NASA International Space Apps Challenge

Aug 2021 - Oct 2021 (3 months)

In the past year the pandemic covid-19 has impacted the way humans live their lives, it has generally affected every aspect of the human culture. To calculate the risk of environmental and socioeconomical impact caused by the covid-19 pandemic. We Team-X came up with an idea of developing an application called Heads Up, which helps to calculate the risk of covid-19 helping stake holders and individuals make guick, fast and credible decisions as regards the covid-19 virus.

So We developed an application which calculates the risk of covid-19 helping stake holders and individuals make quick, fast and credible decisions as regards the covid-19 virus. I personally worked on FrontEnd and or UI/UXof the project.



Senior Web Developer

Curatores Legal Practitioners Sep 2020 - Aug 2021 (1 year) I was the chief technological officer(CTO) at Curatores Legal Practitioners, and I was in-charge of building the company's website, maintaining the company website as well as building other Web products for the company and its affiliates.

Education



🜄 Obafemi Awolowo University

Bachelor's degree, Real Estate 2017 - 2021

Licenses & Certifications



Internet & Web Development Fundamentals - YouAccel 86497474

JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP - YouAccel 68380358

() Jobberman Soft-Skills Training - Jobberman Nigeria ID:3990734

Skills

JavaScript • jQuery • PHP • Real Estate • Graphic Design • Search Engine Optimization (SEO) • Front-end Development • Digital Marketing • Web Development • HTML

Honors & Awards

Galactic Problem Solver - NASA International Space Apps Challenge Oct 2021